想以苗条身形迎接夏日?
Do you want a lean body for summer?
马上行动吧
Well,the time to start is now.
绝非广告噱头 不需地狱式节食abc不需药物辅助
No gimmicks,no crash diets,abcand absolutely no drugs.
想健康的你 将得到健康
Think healthy and be healthy.
行动起来吧
You can start now.
赶快拿起电话 做最好的自己
Just pick up the phone andabcbecome the best you you can be.
卡! 再来一遍
Cut! Going again.
对不起 我把拍摄搞砸了吗?
Sorry,did i mess up the commercial?
不 没关系 你没事吧?
No,it's fine. Are you okay?
我想我胃抽筋了
Ah,i think it's cramps.
火烧火燎似的痛
Oh,i have burning on my side.
坐下来歇会儿 喘口气
Sit down,take a few minutes,abcand catch your breath.
其他人继续跑!
Everybody else keep running!
我们没在拍
We're not filming.
我们不是为了上镜abc而是为了自己
We don't do this for theabccameras. We do it for ourselves.
他坐在这里我们没法拍
We can't go againabcwith him sitting there.
好吧 但这样很假
Fine,um,but that felt phony.
至少也让我跑上一阵
At least let me get a little workout.
没准我和他们喘得一样厉害
Maybe if i'm breathingabcas hard as they are,
好让我没那么像魔鬼训练师
I won't seem like suchabcan evil task master.
好吧 休息五分钟 伙计们
All right,take five,guys.
感觉怎么样?
How you feeling?
我想我准备好了
I think i'm ready to do this.
你确定? 这就对了abc我们就是要这样的斗志
You sure? That's it. That'sabcthe way to fight through.
来吧 力量集中在膝盖
All right,concentrate on those knees.
把重心放上去 抬腿
Lean into it. And lift.
- 抬了abc- 来吧 加油!
- Lifting.abc- Come on,push it!
来吧 顶峰在望
Come on,you're almost at the top.
这八级阶梯是肥胖和苗条的分水岭
Those eight steps are theabcdifference between fat and thin.
七 六 五 四!abc再一步!做得好!
Seven,six, five,four!abcOne more! Nice job!
你感觉火烧火燎?
You feel that burn?
- 脂肪燃烧正为你塑造全新体态abc- 好吧
- That's your body carving out its new shape.abc- Okay.
不要坐下来 慢慢地走下去
Don't sit. Just takeabcit slow on the way down.
天啊
Oh,boy.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
知道为什么我们转介给你abc的病例比平时减少了一半吗?
Any idea why we're getting halfabcas many requests for you as usual?
因为民主党的医疗改革?
Democrats' health care plan?
至少这儿还有个有趣的病例
At least we have one caseabcthat looks intriguing.
30岁的健身教练 突然无法呼吸
30-year-old fitness trainerabcsuddenly can't breathe.
晕倒并摔断了脚踝
Collapses and breaks her ankle.
就这样了? 你不争辩一番abc为什么要让你接这病例?
That's it? You're not gonna argueabcwhy this case is beneath you?
没用 我在电梯里头 跑不了
No point. I'm in anabcelevator. Can't run away.
你在哪里都跑不了
You can't run away anyway.
这话真刻薄
That's just mean.
为什么我们还走在一起?
Why are we still together?
一起去我们的办公室啊
We are going to our office.
人称混淆
Pronoun confusion.
育龄过后妇女的常见症状
Starts kicking in onceabcyou pass child-bearing age.
这才是刻薄
Well,that's just mean.
我的办公室被人捣毁了
My office was recently destroyed.
所以我要征用直接责任人的办公室
I thought i'd use the office ofabcthe doctor directly responsible.
用枪指着我的头的病人abc才负有直接责任
I think the patient holding the gun to myabchead was actually the one directly responsible.
他的牢房塞不下我的桌子
My desk won't fit in his cell.
你可以用外间
You can use our outer office.
Foreman和13到哪里去了?
Where's foreman and thirteen?
楼下临床研究中心
Down in the grc.
13今天开始实验性药物治疗
Thirteen started herabcclinical trials today.
Cuddy在你的办公室干嘛?
What's cuddy doing in your office?
除了用她颠倒八卦仪象的翘臀abc破坏这里的风水以外?
Other than throwing off the feng shui with her assabcthat faces all eight sides of the bagua at once?
- 墙不隔音的abc- 我比你清楚
- These walls aren't soundproof.abc- I'm well aware.
常规CT显示她的肺部问题abc不是由肺本身引起的
Normal ct means that her lung problem has theabcdistinction of having nothing to do with her lungs.
类固醇
Steroids.
没人可以苗条 除非你使诈
No one looks this fit without cheating.
合成类固醇压抑免疫系统abc致使她的肺部易受感染
Anabolic steroids hack away at the immuneabcsystem, left her open to a pulmonary infection.
有肌肉又有曲线
Musclesandcurves.
把我的小弟弟搞糊涂了
My penis is so confused.
她没有服用类固醇
She's not on steroids.
她的节目正是以自然的方式--abc运动 合理膳食等塑造体型
Her program's all about getting in shapeabcnaturally-- exercising,eating right.
你怎么知道?
And you know this because?
她拍资讯型广告推销DVDabc(凌晨播出的购物节目)
She has infomercials to sell her dvds.
怎么了? 我睡得比较晚
What? I'm up late a lot.
而且电视上说什么你都相信
And you actually believeabcwhat you see on tv.
去实验室做测试
Go run the labs.
结果已经出来了abc没有服用类固醇
The labs are back. Andabcthere's no sign of steroid use.
某人能不能先看看她的病历?
Can someone please read her file?
某人能不能别在我们诊断时指手画脚?
Can someone please stopabcbackseat differentialating?
会不会是过敏? 她每天早上都慢跑
What about allergies? Sheabcgoes jogging every morning.
在上班高峰期吸入了汽车尾气
Inhales car fumes during rush hour.
好提议 除了她跑步的地方abc离公路至少半公里
Perfect,except that she was joggingabchalf a mile from the nearest road.
冷空气
In the cold.
冷空气侵入并攻击肺部
Cold air hits the lungs,abcsets off an attack.
运动性哮喘
Exercise-induced asthma.
好提议
Nice try.
除了运动性哮喘不会导致高血压abc拜托先看看病历
Except eia doesn't account for theabcelevated bp, if you'd read the file.
走吧 趁着母夜叉的嚎叫abc还没把我脑筋搅乱
Come on. Before the shriekingabcharpy melts my brain.
- 她的血压正常abc- 我知道
- Her bp's fine.abc- I know.
运动性哮喘符合所有症状
Exercise-induced asthma actually fits.
你知道 我知道 但不能告诉她
I know. You know. She can't know.
证实运动性哮喘的唯一办法abc是还原发病时的情形
The only good way to test for eia is to recreateabcthe conditions in which the attack occurred.
但我们总不能让她拖着abc一条断腿在寒风中慢跑
But we can't exactly make her runabcout in the cold on a broken ankle.
给点创意吧
Get creative.
没事的
It's gonna be okay.
觉得气短么? 胸口发紧?
Any shortness of breath?abcTightness in your chest?
我感觉很好
Feeling pretty good actually.
没有呼吸困难
Not even breathing hard.
血氧和肺活量均在正常范围
O2 stats and lung capacityabcare still well within range.
你的臂带滑下来了 要歇一阵么?
Your cuff's slipping down.abcYou want to stop for a moment?
我不想停 我已经两天没运动了
I'd rather not. Haven't hadabcany exercise in two days.
我想你从不会在饮食中摄入大量脂肪
Take it you don't get aabclot of fat in your diet.
听你的语气 仿佛这不是好事
I take it from your toneabcyou think that's a bad thing.
你从未放纵自我?
Do you ever indulge?
生命中有比放纵一切欲望更重要的事
Ha,there's more to life thanabcindulging your every whim.
我没有说一切
I didn't say every.
但时不时放纵一下abc会让你的生命更--
But a whim every now andabcthen can make life a little--
你还好吗? 呼吸困难么?
you okay?Trouble breathing?
不 我感觉很好 怎么了?
No,i feel fine. Why?
没有脉搏
No pulse.
不是哮喘
This isn't asthma.
还有很多人参加了这个实验?
There a lot of otherabcpeople in the trial?
我同时接收了在慈善医院治疗的病人
I'm taking over the people thatabcalready started it at mercy.
所以人满为患了 停
So pretty full. Stop.
再来一次 不要说话
One more time. No talking.
我不应该这么做
I shouldn't be here.
这是走后门
It's nepotism.
我认识主持实验的人abc所以得到了一个名额
I know the guy running theabcdrug trials, so i get a spot.
你得到这个名额abc是因为你得了亨廷顿症
You have huntington's,abcso you get a spot.
停 再来一次
Stop. One more time.
只动手指 不要动嘴
Just the fingers. No mouth.
这个实验的作用在于abc延长神经细胞的寿命
The point of this thing is toabcimprove neural cell longevity.
在症状出现前 并没有多大作用
Which doesn't matterabcmuch before symptoms.
- 应该把名额让给别人--abc- 闭嘴
- So you should give myabcspot to someone-- - shut up.
停
Stop.
你可以不用内疚了
You can stop feeling guilty.
你的最快敲击频率只有每毫秒.004下
Your best tapping rate was.abc004 taps per millisecond.
意味着你的神经开始退化了
Means your nerves haveabcstarted degenerating.
你想在这里办公?好 我也想
You wanna work in here? Fine. Me too.
这桌子我们五五对分
We'll split the desk, 50-50.
那边是你的 这边是我的
That side's yours. This side's mine.
你说的对 这桌子大得很
You're right. There'sabcplenty of space here.
一个人谁都用不完
Neither one of us needs all of it.
这是你的策略? 以暴制暴?abc这一套对我没用
So that's your strategy. Takingabcthe high road. It's not gonna work.
你说什么?
Did you say something?
桌子太大了 我在对面听不见你说话
I couldn't hear you from all theabcway over here on my side of the desk.
病人一度停止心跳
Patient's heart stopped.
我们电击使她回复窦性心律abc现在情况稳定了
We shocked her back toabcsinus rhythm. She's stable.
不是测试引发的 心电图正常
Test didn't set itabcoff. Her ekg was normal.
还是那句话
Well,she's consistent.
肺的问题不是由肺本身引起的
The lung problems hadabcnothing to do with her lungs.
心脏问题也不是心脏本身引起
A heart problem that hasabcnothing do with her heart.
某个东西正在扼杀她的系统
Something is strangling her system.
良性肿瘤?
Carcinoid tumor?
把它找出来切除
Find it,cut it out.
乳房假体渗漏会不会导致关节痛?
Can a leaking breastabcimplant cause joint pain?
不会 显然她没有隆胸
No. And she clearlyabcdoesn't have implants.
也没有关节痛 怎么回事?
Or joint pain. What's going on?
是别的病人
Got another patient.
我开了一个在线第二意见诊所
I set up an onlineabcsecond opinion clinic.
有的病人不相信自己的医生abc就用电邮发来他们的症状
People who don't like or trustabctheir doctors email symptoms.
一顿午饭我能搞定四五个病例
I can knock off four orabcfive cases over lunch.
靠回电邮就能进账2000刀
Clear two grand by emailing them back.
升结肠没有问题
Ascending colon's clean.
这样做是违法的
That's got to be illegal.
只在九个州违法abc这个州不是其中之一
Only in nine states, andabcthis isn't one of them.
我贴出了法律告示abc申明这不能取代现场诊断
Legal notice spells out itabcdoesn't replace doctor's visits,
所以不会因误诊而遭到控告
So there's no opportunityabcfor malpractice.
为什么从未听你提起这事?
How come you haven'tabcsaid anything about this?
这不是什么大秘密abc我也不是多嘴的人
It's no big secret. I guessabci'm just not very chatty.
你续订国家地理杂志都告诉我们了
You told us when you renewed yourabcsubscription tonational geographic.
小肠没有问题 移到幽门
Small intestine looks clean.abcMoving into the pylorus.
那么说你不介意我知会House?
So you don't mind if i tell house?
实际上 House也许会介意abc因为这是以他的名义开的
Actually house may sort of mind becauseabci sort of set it up in house's name.
胆管没问题
Nothing in the bile duct.
"以他的名义"是什么意思?
And by "set it up inabchis name," you mean?
即是Gregory House的第二意见门诊abc所有医学建议由Gregory House亲自提出
I mean,it's dr. Gregory house's second opinion clinicabcwith medical advice direct from dr. Gregory house.
你脑子秀豆了 你死期不远矣
You're insane. With two days to live.
House永不会发现
House is never gonna find out.
除非我告密
He will if i tell him.
要么你分我30% 我替你保密
Or you cut me in for 30%abcand i keep your secret safe.
- 你这是敲诈abc- 正是
- That's blackmail.abc- Yes.
移到--
Movingabcinto the--
这是她的胃?
That's her stomach?
只有小玻璃杯那么大
It's the size of a shot glass.
因为我们的病人是个大骗子
Because our patient's a big,fat cheater.
厉害
Subtle.
你们这帮天才居然能发现
No way you geniusesabccould've spotted this.
胃旁路手术 她把胃缝小了
Gastric bypass surgery.abcShe had her stomach stapled.
术后把记录从病历抽出abc以免影响她的DVD销量
Then had the records from her filesabcpulled so it wouldn't ruin their dvd sales.
你们能出去谈吗?
Can you do this outside?
可以 但就失去我特意在这里谈的意义了
I could, but that would defeatabcthe purpose of doing it here.
我的得力助手哪儿去了?
Where are the smart guys?
如果你指的是Foreman和13
If you mean foreman and thirteen,
首次预约治疗要花一天时间
Apparently the first appointment ofabcthe drug trial's an all-day thing.
我居然批准了?
I said yes to this?
- 胃旁路手术可能会引起--abc- 别管旁路了
- Her gastric bypass procedureabccould cause-- - forget the bypass.
把她当成胖妞治
Treat her like a fat girl.
干脆把她当60岁的亚裔老头子治得了abc她一点也不胖
Should we treat her like a 60-year-oldabcasian man too? She's not fat.
外表而已
Not on the outside.
内里可是大有乾坤
But on the inside,abcshe's still tons of fun.
她瘦下去之前abc也许患有Ⅱ型糖尿病
When she was obese, sheabcprobably had type two diabetes.
造成了永久性的神经损伤
Could've left her withabcpermanent nerve damage.
顺着我说的想得10分
Ten points for doing what i said.
顺着我说的想错了 倒扣10分
Minus ten points for doing it badly.
如果是糖尿病引发的神经损伤abc不会等到几年后才发作
If this was diabetes-induced rveabcdamage, it would've kicked in years ago.
你看到我的球了吗?abc(另意为睾丸)
Have you seen my balls?
稍等一下好吗?
Can you hold on a second?
我的球 你看到我的球了吗?
My balls. Have you seen my balls?
大球和红球
Giant one and the red one.
- 这招是不会奏效的abc- 当然会
- Your plan isn't gonna work.abc- It is.
我要让你痛苦好把你逼走
I try to make youabcmiserable to make you leave.
你拒绝承认这让你很痛苦
You deny that it's making you miserable.
接着你会反过来让我痛苦abc好阻止我让你痛苦
You try to make me miserable soabci'll stop making you miserable.
到头来你会被迫离开abc并列出一堆与痛苦无关的理由
And eventually youwillleave, citingabcreasons that have nothing to do with misery.
你再饶舌也烦不了我
You're not bothering me.
第一步成功
Step one complete.
我用手机打给你
I'm gonna call you from my cell.
然后我会回来这里
And then i will come back in here.
喂 我得向他解释 我把球藏起来了abc而且不会还给他
Yeah,i just had to explain to him that iabchad his balls and he's not getting them back.
麻烦借过
'Scuse me.
睡眠呼吸中止解释了--
Sleep apneaabcexplains--
当她收缩成瘦子abc呼吸中止症状就会消失
apnea would've disappearedabcwhen she shrank.
如果她的气管的肌肉组织abc受到破坏就不会了
Not if it destroyed theabcmusculature of her trachea.
呼吸中止切断了供应大脑的氧气
Apnea cuts off oxygen to the brain.
- 导致神经损伤--abc- 她打鼾么?
- The resulting neurologicalabcdamage-- - she been snoring?
她没提过
She didn't mention it.
她提过她睡了一夜之后abc还是会很疲倦么?
Did she mention feeling tiredabcafter a full night's sleep?
- 没有 但-abc- 不是睡眠中止
- No,but-- -abcthis isn't apnea.
还有这蠢房子不适合做鉴别诊断
And this is a stupidabcroom to be doing a ddx in.
长话短说
Cliff notes.
胃旁路手术让她外表变苗条了
Gastric bypass only makesabcher skinny on the outside.
但里头得了非心肺本身导致的心肺问题
On the inside,we have heart and lungabcissues not caused by heart and lung issues.
这是私人空间 House 病例可以等
Private area,house. It can wait.
可能是胃旁路手术的副作用
You need to consider side effectsabcfrom her gastric bypass surgery.
- 别管旁路了--abc- 让这快死的女孩把话说完
- Forget the bypass.abc- Let the dying girl finish.
是你说别管旁路的--
You saidabcforget the--
13医生有发言权
Dr. Thirteen has the floor.
胃旁路可能会导致营养不良
Bypass could createabcmalabsorption issues.
造成低钾
Leads to low potassium.
非常烂 她的钾水平正常
Very stupid. Her potassium's fine.
但她的肠道不是
But her intestines aren't.
胃旁路可能会引起盲袢综合征abc导致营养不良
Gastric bypass could cause malabsorptionabcby creating a blind loop of bowel.
小肠蠕动产生溃烂
It ulcerates during exercise.
细菌随着血液流动
Bacteria get loose in the bloodstream.
转移至心脏和肺部
Migrate to the heart and lungs.
非常不烂
Very not stupid.
肠道里有细菌abc意味着大便里也有
Bacteria in the bowels meansabcthere's bacteria in the poop.
去取来做测试
Get some and test it.
他在医院任何角落都能得出abc小肠细菌过度生长的结论
He could've come up with siboabcanywhere else in the hospital.
你何必来跑来这里干扰我们治疗
You didn't need to comeabcdown here and screw with us.
她的错误想法使他得出了正确诊断
But her wrong idea led to his right one.
干扰一下就能救命
It was vital screwing.
我们认为 你以前的手术abc引起小肠细菌过度生长的症状
We think your surgery might'veabccaused an infection called sibo.
粪便化验可以帮我们确诊
Stool tests will help us to confirm.
把大便排到这里面
Put some of what you're full of in here.
如果有手术可以增高 你会做吗?
If surgery could somehow makeabcyou taller, wouldn't you do it?
当然
Sure.
但我不会找来一帮小矮人
But i wouldn't call aabcmeeting of the lollipop guild
告诉他们只要努力锻炼就能长高
And tell them they can growabcif they work real hard at it.
我没有劝说任何人不要做胃旁路手术
I don't tell anyone notabcto get gastric bypass.
我只是告诉他们如何保持健康
I tell them how to get healthy.
如何提高生活质量
How to improve their lives.
是的 让他们做你自己都不愿做的事
Yeah,by telling them to doabcwhat you were unwilling to.
我愿意做任何事
I was willing to do anything.
甲状腺荷尔蒙 地狱式减肥abc全部不起作用
Thyroid,hormones, crashabcdiets-- none of it worked.
我的身体像个监狱
My body was like a prison.
当我做完手术 我得到了健康
When i got the surgery, i got healthy.
当我得到健康 我也得到了快乐
And when i got healthy, i got happy.
我看不出你有多快乐
I'm not sure you're happy.
即使你快乐 也不是因为健康abc而是因为变漂亮了
But if you are, being healthyabcdidn't do it. Being pretty did.
大便排在盆子里
Poop in the bedpan.
你占用了House的办公室?
House's office? Really?
是他让你来求情的吗?
Did he send you here to beg for it back?
医院里还有上百号医生--
Well,there are dozensabcof other doctors--
其他医生要在办公室里干无聊的事abc比如说给病人看病
Other doctors actually use their officesabcfor crazy stuff like seeing patients.
而不是往墙上扔扔球 就当工作
Not throwing a ball againstabcthe wall and calling it work.
他有他的方法 那个球能救命
It's his process. That ball saves lives.
这是他给你的理由?
Did he give you talking points?
是 但我也有自己的理由
Yeah,but i added one of my own.
你占用他的办公室abc不仅仅为了办公室
Don't take his office and pretend likeabcall you're doing is taking his office.
你选他的房间 是因为你想呆在里面
You chose his room becauseabcyou want to be there.
但光坐在他旁边发白日梦abc是不会成事的
But sitting near him andabchoping isn't gonna get it done.
给我出去 不然我就要征用你的办公室了
Leave here now, orabci'll take your office.
不 你不会的
No,you won't.
那个隆胸女又发邮件来了abc这次说她有慢性疲劳问题
The boob lady emailed me againabccomplaing of chronic fatigue now.
硬说是义乳造成的
She's convinced theabcimplants are responsible.
- 没有关系abc- 我跟她说了
- They're not.abc- I told her.
她说要是我找不出病因abc就去执照委员会投诉我
She says something is, and if i don't find outabcwhat she's gonna complain to the licensing board.
- 这不好笑abc- 很好笑
- It's not funny.abc- It is.
你体会不到它的搞笑之处abc是因为它将毁了你的事业
You just can't appreciate it becauseabcit's gonna destroy your career.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
又叫Foreman "干净 发音清晰的黑佬"?abc(引奥巴马)
He call foreman "cleanabcand articulate" again?
好大的胆子
It is surprising.
门诊病人有怨言罢了
Clinic patients just whining.
便便怎么样了?
What's the poop?
还要1小时才能分离出样本
It's gonna take about anabchour to spin down the sample.
我们要找什么?
What are we looking for?
你不知道么?
You don't know?
我在践行苏格拉底式的思辨
I'm doing my famous socrates impression.
我能把口音仿得很像
Think i really nailed the accent.
高脂肪含量指向小肠细菌过度生长
High fat content indicates sibo.
脂肪在水里会怎么样?
And what does fat do in water?
漂浮
It floats.
还有什么会浮在水面?
What else floats in water?
正确答案是小鸭子
Correct answer is a duck.
如果它浮不起来 就是Kutner错了
If it doesn't float,abckutner missed the boat.
看来我把呼吸中止排除是错的
Looks like i was wrong to dismiss apnea.
你们今晚可以通宵呆在abc睡眠实验室里庆祝
You guys can stay up all nightabcgloating in the sleep lab.
会不会是隆胸留下的abc疤痕组织的问题? 可能--
What about all that scar tissueabcaround the implant?Could that be--
这种程度的增生很正常
that amount of encapsulation'sabcperfectly normal.
我总得给她个解释吧
Well,i gotta tell her something.
让她找个像样的整形医生 做些矫正
Tell her to find a decent plasticabcsurgeon who can correct the placement--
是啊 她巴不得听到这话abc她把不舒服归罪于胸部不对称
Yeah,that's what she wants toabchear, she's sick and she's lopsided.
就跟她说是病毒
Tell her it's a virus.
有这可能 这样她就不会纠缠你了--abcEmmy的脑电图呈直线
It probably is, and it'll get her off yourabcback for a few-- emmy's eeg is flatlining.
她去哪了?
Where would she have gone?
嘿 我刚看见你们在监控室里忙呢
Hey,i looked for you guys in theabccontrol room, but you seemed busy.
快下来 你上次锻炼 心脏就出了问题
Get off there. Last time youabcexercised, you had a cardiac incident.
我好着呢
I feel fine.
你上次也一样
You felt fine last time.
我只睡了几小时 但我感觉挺好
I only slept a coupleabchours, but i feel great.
我能弄一台这机器么?
Can i get one of those machines?
你脚踝骨折了 还跑步
You're running on a broken ankle.
一点也不疼
It doesn't hurt.
你的腿在流血
And your leg is bleeding.
- 有感觉么?abc- 这说明什么?
- You feel that?abc- What does that mean?
左脚的麻痹延伸到腿部
Numbness in her left footabcis ascending into her leg.
她怎么能溜出去跑步的?
How did she manage toabcsneak out for a run?
她说她要去洗手间
She said she needed to use the bathroom.
你俩去做睡眠呼吸中止症的测试abc这个用不着去洗手间吧?
You two get the results of the sleep apneaabctest, or did those need to use the bathroom too?
脑电图的α波已经排除了这个可能
Alpha waves on the eeg ruled it out.
我因正当理由混合了些氢硫化物abc不小心漏了一些出来
I was mixing some hydrogen sulfide for good andabcvalid reasons and must've spilled some on my side.
你那边也闻得到么?
Did it waft over to your side?
真狡猾啊
Cunning plan.
你肯定知道abc这两边都得难闻好几个小时
You do realize it's gonnaabcstink for hours on both sides.
哦 看看都几点了?
Oh,would you look at the time?
希望你的病人已经没事了
I hope your patient isn't still sick...
不然你就得在这里通宵啦
Forcing you to stay here all night.
麻痹的延伸 说明神经受损
Ascending numbness meansabcher nerves are breaking down.
- 或者大脑abc- 或者二者都有
- Or her brain.abc- Or both.
- 我们得走了abc- 等我弄完就下去找你
- We've gotta go.abc- Let me finish. I'll meet you down there.
你昨天迟到了15分钟
You were 15 minutes late yesterday.
我不想你养成坏习惯
I don't want you to develop bad habits.
谢谢这生活一课 但15分钟时间差没什么
Appreciate the life lesson, but 15 minutesabcgive or take isn't gonna make a difference.
先给别的病人看吧
Get started on your other patients.
这里解决了我就下去
I'll be down there when we're done here.
真了不起 知道是谁罩你呢abc丫头 来击个掌!
Way to know where your breadabcis buttered,sister. Up high!
如果问题出在大脑 可能是多发性硬化症
If the problem's in herabcbrain,it could be ms.
或者早发性帕金森症
Or early onset parkinson's.
如果问题出在神经 可能是横贯性脊髓炎
But if it's her nerves, itabccould be transverse myelitis.
或其他无数个原因
Or a million other things.
如果解决不了这问题abc就得在这待到天黑了
We're gonna stay in theabcdark until we can figure out
如果电力问题出在发电站或高压线上
If her electrical problem is in her powerabcstation or in the high-tension wires.
发电站就是大脑 高压线就是神经
Power station's the brain.abcWires are the nerves.
去做个神经传导速度测试
Go run an ncv test.
这个测试可以测量abc电脉冲在神经内传导所需的时间
The test will measure the amount of time it'll takeabcthis electrical impulse to travel along your nerves.
- 会疼么?abc- 不会 把胳膊伸出来
- Will it hurt?abc- No. Give me your arm.
你可以和蔼一点
You can ask nicely.
我在医学院学到 亲切是治不了病的
I learned at med school youabcdon't actually cure with kindness.
你说得对 我真虚伪
You're right. I'm a hypocrite.
但我别无选择
But i don't have a choice.
我对你的解释没兴趣
Not really interestedabcin your rationalizations.
如果把胃旁路术的事说出去abc就再也不会有人相信我了
If i'm open about the gastric bypass,abcno one would listen to me anymore.
你是说 没人买你的DVD了
You mean no one would buy your dvds.
这不是DVD销量的问题
It's not about the dvd sales.
我在帮助别人
I'm helping people.
我的客户追求健康
My clients are makingabcthemselves healthy.
他们在更好地生活
They're living better lives.
你就真能告诉我 你从来没虚伪过?
Can you honestly tell me you'veabcnever done anything hypocritical?
我敢说你也有充分的理由
I'm sure you had good reasons.
请...把胳膊伸出来好么?
Give me your arm... Please?
举着胳膊 别放下
Keep your arm raised.
这是不是说我的神经有问题?
Does this mean somethingabcis wrong with my nerves?
不是 是你的肌肉
No. It's your muscles.
这测试没必要做了
We don't need to run this test.
病情并非如我们所想
It's not what we thought.
她肌肉无力 可能是重症肌无力的前兆
She has muscle weakness. Couldabcindicate myasthenia gravis.
是啊
Yep.
也可能是某种毒素
Also could be some kind of toxin.
不好意思 你是去人事处么?
Excuse me,are you goingabcup to the personnel floors?
我要见House医生
I'm going to see dr. House.
你有预约过么?
Do you have an appointment with him?
互发过些邮件
We've been emailing.
我有关节痛 疲劳 托它俩的福
Joint pain and fatigue thanks to these.
- 我敢肯定没什么事abc- 哦 现在又这样
- I'm sure it's nothing.abc- Oh,and now this.
- 他其实在楼下呢abc- 呃 他不在 下班了
- He's actually downstairs.abc- Uh,gone. Gone for the day.
我们在他手下工作 可以帮你安排急诊
But,uh,we work for him. Weabccan set you up in the e.r.
抗生素会让她感觉好些abc明早之前她必须离开这里
The antibiotics will make her feelabcbetter. She's outta here by morning.
- 得是葡萄球菌感染才行abc- 肯定是啦
- If it is a staph infection.abc- It's gotta be.
她胳膊上都是纹身 还有穿孔abc谁知道是在哪弄的
She has sleeves of tattoos andabcpiercings from god knows where.
她肌肉无力
She has muscle weakness.
可能是重症肌无力的前兆
Could indicate myasthenia gravis.
我做了个巨诡异的梦
I had the weirdest dream.
你们按时做完了测试
You guys did the test inabca reasonable amount of time
在我打瞌睡之前就回来了
And came back here beforeabci had time to fall asleep.
还能闻到那味不?
You guys still smell that?
也许应该把你的办公室给她
Maybe you should justabclet her have your office.
或者...
Or...
她可以把你们的办公室收回abc再抽几间作停尸房
She sends one of yours to the hospital,abcsend one of hers to the morgue.
不是重症肌无力
It's not myasthenia gravis.
她的呼吸好转 四肢出现肌无力
Her breathing's improving and theabcweakness is in her extremities.
可能是对肉毒杆菌的反应
Could be a botulinum reaction.
我觉得你肆意破坏上司的办公室abc算不上是绝妙的反击
I don't think sabotaging your boss'abcoffice is a wise counterattack.
睁只眼闭只眼 邪恶就能得逞啦
All that is need for evil to succeedabcis for good men to do nothing.
- 她可能用过很多A型肉毒杆菌 紧致皮肤abc- 没错
- She probably used a lot of botox to tighten up her skin.abc- True.
也可能是某种重金属中毒
Could also be any kindabcof heavy metal toxicity.
海鲜吃太多 摄入贝毒素或砷
Psp or arsenic fromabceating too much seafood.
劣质瓶装水里含镉
Cadmium from bad bottled water.
罐装水果和天然谷物里含铅或镍
Lead or nickel from cannedabcfruits or natural grains.
修缮计划里没包括更换那个
I don't think replacing thatabcwas part of the renovation plans.
现在包括啦
It is now.
我们运气好abc那些毒素都能用螯合治疗
Lucky for us,we can treat all thoseabctoxins with the same thing: chelation.
你压根没来
You never showed up.
从我房间出去
Get out of my house.
我想找到证据abc证明你又回到了自甘堕落的状态
I wanted to find proof that you were slippingabcback into your self-destructive pattern.
证明你不值得我花心思
Confirm you weren't worth my time.
相反地 我找到了这个
Instead, i found this.
你遵循了我所有的指示
You followed all of myabcinstructions to the letter.
也许是认真的那个
Probably better than any patient i have.
那为什么只有你没来治疗呢?
So why are you the only one whoabccan't show up for appointments?
House的活一办完 我就下去了
I came down right afterabci was finished with house.
你在办公室治疗另一位病人
You were in your officeabcwith another patient.
等待室里还有一个病人
And there was anotherabcpatient in the waiting room.
Janice
Janice.
接下来的8到10年中abc身体将发生怎样的变化 我非常清楚
I'm well-aware of what's gonna happen toabcmy body over the next eight to ten years.
我想每次走进那里abc视觉影像反复提醒我这个现实
I do not need a visual reminderabcevery time i walk into that place.
可以理解
That's understandable.
人天性如此
It's human.
而你需要克服它
And you need to get over it.
明天按时来治疗 不然就再也别来了
Now you show up on time tomorrow,abcor you don't show up at all.
你妈妈要走了
Your mom is leaving.
你这辈子都会因此后悔的!
You're gonna regret thisabcthe rest of your life.
螯合作用不管用
The chelation didn't work.
她的肌肉持续退化
Her muscles are still deteriorating.
排除毒素的可能
Rules out toxins.
在兴登堡通货紧缩的时候 又出啥问题了?abc(波兰南部城市)
So what else can go wrongabcwhen the hindenburg deflates?
我们为啥不能在你办公室讨论?
Why aren't we doing this in your office?
很明显 办公室里没有家具abc还在那讨论多傻啊
Obviously because it would be stupid toabcdo this in an office with no furniture.
Cuddy...对我的过激行为反应过度了
Cuddy... Overreacted to my overreaction.
冠状动脉心瘘 即使小洞也会导致--
Coronaro-cardiac fistula.Evenabca small hole could cause--
这是肺原发的 不是心脏
this started in theabclungs, not the heart.
你为啥朝远离Foreman的方向斜倚45度?
And why are you leaning on aabc45-degree angle away from foreman?
我坐得直直的
I'm sitting straight.
在希望的田野上 希望落空了?
Trouble in the land of false hope?
一切都好着呢 可能是奥地利综合症
Everything's fine. Austrian syndrome.
挺会转移话题
Nice deflection.
但病人不喝酒 她是个养生狂
But our patient doesn'tabcdrink. She's a health nut.
就算我愤世嫉俗 觉得她在撒谎
And even if i was a cynical guyabcand thought that she was a liar,
做了毒理检验 结果是酒精阴性
I'd have done a tox screen whichabcwould've come back negative for alcohol.
你们也该常来聚一聚
You should come to theseabcgatherings more often.
看上去就不会像个傻瓜了
Keep you from looking like an idiot.
你是要打赌 还是病人又出状况了?
Are you making book, or didabcsomething else happen to our patient?
是私事 我调成震动吧
Personal. I'll put it on vibrate.
格林-巴利综合征
Guillain-barre.
病发时通常有肌肉疼痛abc病人以为是运动过度
Usually starts as a muscle pain patientsabccompare to the pain of over-exercising.
谁呼你? 是你老婆么?
So who's paging you? Your wife?
她先呼了Kutner 你担心不?
Does it worry you thatabcshe paged kutner first?
格林-巴利综合征说得通
Guillain-barre fits.
病人没注意到初期症状abc因为她每天都肌肉酸痛
Patient didn't notice the initial symptoms becauseabcit's no different than how she feels every day.
她肌肉无力是全身瘫痪的前兆
Her muscle weakness is theabcprecursor to full paralysis.
胃旁路术可能是元凶
Gastric bypass probably set it off.
哦 美丽的代价多沉重啊
Oh,at what price beauty?
给她用血浆清除术
Go start her on plasmapheresis.
* 她把莱檬放到椰子里 一饮而尽 *
* she put the lime in theabccoconut, she drank it all up *
Dee Dee
dee dee.
你能不能别唱了?
Can you stop singing?
音乐自动症
Musical automatism.
她可能正有部分癫痫发作
She could be having aabcpartial seizure right now.
- 你们得去找Houseabc- Dee dee!
- you need to get house.abc- Dee dee!
冲她大吼可不是有效的疗法
Yelling at her is not goingabcto be an effective treatment.
她是装的 是想引起注意
She's faking. It's a cry for attention.
她的大脑可能都熄火了
her brain could be misfiring.
是啊 罕见的神经障碍abc这比引人注意更有可能
Right,a rare neurological disorder isabcfar more likely than a cry for attention.
我是说 这女人没什么要紧的症状
I mean,nothing about thisabcwoman screams "look at me."
恰恰相反 瞧瞧
On the other hand, look at her.
她得做全套神经系统检查
she needs a full neurological work-up.
快去找House!
get house!
真是绝顶讽刺啊
ultimate irony.
想变得健康 却害了我自己
Killed myself tryingabcto make myself healthy.
你不会死的 明白么?
You're not dying,okay?
这病可以控制
This disease is manageable.
最好还是习惯一下轮椅吧
Better start gettingabcused to that wheelchair.
自我怜悯不适合你
Self-pity doesn't suit you.
- 就扶我下去...abc- 不行
- Just take meabcdown to the-- - no.
你自己能走
You're strong enough to walk.
来吧 自己下床走
Come on,get your assabcout of bed and walk.
可能是动脉瘤
Could be an aneurysm.
我们得控制住她的血压abc给她用钙通道阻滞剂
We've got to control her blood pressure.abcStart her on a calcium channel blocker.
或者...你可以告诉House
Or... You could tell house.
我们不能告诉House
We can't tell house.
你们麻烦大了
You'll be in trouble.
说回来 她的确有病
On the other hand, she's sick.
她只是唱唱歌
She's singing.
她耳道出血 头发脱落
And bleeding out of herabcears, and losing her hair.
动脉瘤无法解释关节痛
An aneurysm doesn'tabcexplain her joint pain.
威尔森氏症可以解释
Wilson's disease does.
没有角膜色素环
No kayser-fleischer rings.
厌食症
Anorexia.
你慌不择路了
Now you're just desperate.
胆道肿瘤造成了去肿瘤综合症
Biliary tumor causingabcpareneoplastic syndrome.
没准就是这个
That might actually fit.
我去做扫描 确认一下
I'll scan to confirm.
- 你要帮我做?abc- 你没空嘛
- You'd do that for me?abc- You don't have the time.
意味着我可以分得25%收入abc你没法说不
Which means i can ask for 25% ofabcyour income and you'll give it to me.
你要翻墙么?
You going over the fence?
我跑了三趟abc才让承包商相信我是Cuddy的上司
Took three visits, but i finally convincedabcthe contractor that i'm cuddy's boss.
所有修缮计划都得经过我同意
And all the office renovationabcplans need to go through me.
你事前确实衡量过吧?
You did do the math on this,right?
在她办公室捣乱abc只能让修理工作拖得更久
Screwing with her office meansabcher renovations will take longer.
就是说 她得在你办公室待更长时间
Means she will be in your office longer.
看见没?
See there?
我在放马桶的地方换了个坐浴盆
I'm having a bidet putabcin instead of a toilet.
不是外加的 是彻底换掉了
Not in addition to. Instead of.
知道那旧马桶咋回事不?
You want to know whatabchappened to the old toilet?
她得继续跟你挤办公室abc你嘴上还说不想跟她一块
She'll be with you whereabcyou claim to not want her.
我用大锤把它敲碎了
I smashed it with a sledgehammer.
在某些古文明中 这可被看作是求婚呐
I think in some ancient cultures that wasabcactually considered a proposal of marriage.
你觉得这好玩不?
Is this fun for you?
把别人的乐趣都分析没了?
Analyzing everyone else's fun away?
约她出去吧
Ask her out.
医院能省下好大一笔钱呢
It'll cost the hospital a lot less.
我带来些亲友团 让你开心开心
I brought some visitors. Cheer you up.
没事 进来吧 大家
It's okay. Come on in,guys.
我们都坚持着健康计划呢 没人作弊
We're all staying on yourabcplan. Nobody's cheating.
这太好了
That's great.
呃 你坐到我胳膊上了
Uh,you're on my arm.
我们知道你做了胃旁路术
We found out about your gastric bypass.
你怎么能这样欺骗我们?
How could you lie to us like that?
是医生告诉你们的?
The doctors told you?
你弄疼我的胳膊了
You're really hurting my arm.
你不是口口声声说的好人
You're not the best you you can be.
你是个骗子
You're a fraud.
你是个痛恨自己的胖子
You're a self-hating fat person.
你真的弄疼我了
You're really hurting me.
感受燃烧的快感吧
Feel the burn.
救命啊!
Help!
从我身上下来! 快从我身上下来!
Get off of me! Get offabcof me! Get off of me!
心境一致幻觉
Mood congruent hallucinations.
说明不是格林-巴利综合征
Means it's not guillain-barre.
就是说 不管是啥问题 都不出在大脑
Which means whatever itabcis, it's now in her brain.
你要去哪?
Where are you going?
抱歉 去治疗
Sorry. Treatment.
Foreman是按时钟给你排预约
Does foreman schedule yourabcappointments by numbers on the clock
还是专拣我忙的时候?
Or just by when i'm inabcthe middle of something?
真抱歉 我死得不是时候
Sorry if i'm dyingabcat a bad time for you.
可能是中枢神经系统淋巴瘤
Could be cns lymphoma.
减了两百磅就只是凑巧咯?
So losing the 200 poundsabcwas just a coincidence?
会不会是朊病毒病?
What about a prion disease?
要是她的大脑逐渐变得千疮百孔abc我们就无能为力了
If her brain is slowly turning into aabcswiss cheese, there's not a lot we can do.
倒是有些可能的疗法
There are some possible treatments.
活检她的大脑 确认一下
Get a brain biopsy to confirm.
做测试之前 不准你开这女人的脑
You're not cutting into thisabcwoman's brain before you test.
这就是个测试
Thatisthe test.
你不是想测试中枢神经系统淋巴瘤abc这是个很合理的诊断
Not for cns lymphoma, which isabca perfectly legitimate diagnosis.
可以用非侵入式方法测试
One you can test for non-invasively.
你明显对侵略性没什么意见
You're obviously notabcopposed to being invasive.
先排除中枢神经系统淋巴瘤abc再排除星形细胞瘤
Rule out cns lymphoma first,abcthen rule out astrocytoma,
再排除其他脑部肿瘤
then rule out other brain tumors.
特此宣布它们都被排除了
I hereby declare them ruled out.
做测试去
Run the tests.
你可以做脑部活检 但只作为最后手段
You can do a brain biopsy,abcbut only as a last resort.
照着Cuddy的清单 逐个排除吧
Start running down cuddy'sabclist of diseases it's not.
你不是因为医疗理由才阻止我
You're not stoppingabcme for medical reasons.
你阻止我...
You're stopping me...
是因为你对我有意思
Because you have the hots for me.
你还待在这 说明你也对我有意思
You're still here becauseabcyou have the hots for me.
证据事实表明 是我搬到你办公室里的
Evidenced by the fact that i'mabcthe one who moved into your office.
这间办公室最大 又不是我弄坏了--
It's the biggest office.Andabci'm not the one that destroyed--
你为啥穿成这样?
why are you dressed like that?
你为什么总是拼命吸引我注意?
Why do you try so hardabcto get my attention?
你是在挑逗我么?
Are you screwing with me?
这取决于你的回答
That depends on your answer.
我们之间总会发生些什么
Everybody knows this is going somewhere.
我想现在该接吻了
I think we're supposed to kiss now.
我们早就吻过了
We already did that.
- 这算下一步 也挺符合逻辑的abc- 是么?
- It seemed like the logical next step.abc- Really?
我还为此而吃惊 真是白痴啊
I'm an idiot for being surprised.
能把它们留下么?
Can you leave these?
我会坚持来的 但能给我改个时间么?
I'll keep coming, but can youabcchange my appointment time?
不行 日程都排满了
Can't. Schedule's full.
反正铁定是跟她一起了abc倒不如去认识认识
You're stuck with her. Mightabcas well get to know her.
你的头部核磁共振很正常abc说明不是中枢神经系统淋巴瘤
Your head mri was clean. Meansabcyou don't have cns lymphoma.
清单上还有什么?
What's next on the list?
其他脑部肿瘤
Other types of brain tumors.
能在餐厅停一下么?
Can we stop at the cafeteria?
我可以给你打包点吃的 想吃什么?
I can have something broughtabcup for you. What do you want?
巧克力蛋糕
Chocolate cake.
你不能放弃 我们会找出病因的
You can't give up. We'reabcgonna figure this out.
我还应该期待些什么?
What am i supposed to be hoping for?
难道期待我脑部有肿瘤?
That you find a brain tumor?
还有什么可能?
What else could it be?
我撒了谎 你对我那么严厉
You were so hard on me about lying.
你也照做一回 告诉我事实如何?
How about you take some of yourabcown advice and tell me the truth?
单子上还写了什么?
What's next on the list?
阮病毒病
Prion disease.
如果我得了这病 能有多糟?
And if that's what i got, how bad?
疗法是有一些 但不能保证治愈
There are a few treatments,abcbut there's no guarantee.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
那你还连块蛋糕都不让我吃?
And you won't let meabchave a piece of cake?
呃 Cuddy在哪呢?
Uh,where's cuddy?
不是中枢神经系统淋巴瘤
It's not cns lymphoma.
我知道
I know.
她状况更糟了abc要我去找Cuddy同意脑部活检么?
She's getting worse. You want me to find cuddyabcand get her approval for the brain biopsy?
你出轨了 没受惩罚 有啥感觉?
When you were philandering withabcimpunity, how did that feel?
表面很享受
Superficially,i loved it.
内心觉得自己很可悲
But deep down,i think i was miserable.
怎么? 出什么事了?
Why? What's going on?
你并不可悲
You weren't miserable.
你为这段感情放弃了一些东西
You gave something away toabcmake a relationship work.
你找借口说是为了找回一些东西
You rationalize that you'reabcgetting something back.
我去让Cuddy批准脑部切片检查
Okay,i'm gonna go get cuddy'sabcapproval for the brain biopsy.
不用了 我自己去做检查吧
Leave 'em there. I'mabcgonna do the biopsy myself.
Cuddy想让我们排除七个不同的东西
Cuddy wanted us to eliminateabcseven different things.
Cuddy不能总如她所愿
Cuddy doesn't always get what she wants.
向有权利的人施压可不是个好主意
Bad idea to get into a power playabcwith somebody who has the power.
你被解雇了
You're fired.
为了证明你说的是对的
Just reinforcing your point.
不管你在玩什么把戏 应该聪明点
Whatever personal drama you're playingabcout, you'd be a lot smarter to--
我以为你说她病了
Thought you said she was sick.
病人不会自己恢复的
Sick people don'tabcspontaneously get better.
会的 有种东西叫免疫系统
Yes,they do. It'sabccalled an immune system.
严重到让我来治疗的病人不会这样的
Sick people who are sick enough to makeabcit to me don't spontaneously get better.
虽然讲起来啰嗦 不过更精确了
Not as pithy,but yeah,abctechnically more accurate.
你上次给她做什么了?
What's the last thing you gave her?
我带她做了磁共振
I took her for anabcmri looking for--
磁共振只是检查 不是治疗
mri's detect.They don't treat.
磁共振后给她吃什么药了?
What did you give her after the mri?
什么也没给她吃
I didn't give her anything.
病因不明让她情绪低落
She got depressed atabcthe lack of direction.
我们去餐厅吃了些巧克力蛋糕
We went to the cafeteriaabcfor some chocolate cake.
带她回了房间 打了维他命点滴 让她休息
Took her to her room, hungabca bana bag, let her rest.
你给她吃蛋糕了?
You gave her cake.
她自己想要的 我没当回事
She asked forabcit.I figured--
你预备让我再提20个问题 才告诉我吗?
you figured you'd let me play 20abcquestions instead of just telling me.
又不高兴了呗?
Feeling crappy again?
我给你带来良药了
I brought your cure.
本来想给你输液的abc但是这些东西可能会堵塞滴管的
I'd give you an iv of this stuff, but theabcfrosting tends to get stuck in the little tubes.
-开玩笑呢么?abc-不是玩笑 也不是谎话
- Is this a joke?abc- It's not a joke. Not a lie.
从来没想过欺骗你
Not an attempt to defraud in any way.
这是一名合格的医生作出的正确诊断
It's an actual licensed physicianabcwith an actual diagnosis.
遗传性粪卟啉症
Hereditary coproporphyria.
你遗传的外貌受到眷顾
Your face is genetically blessed.
但遗传到的身体机能就没那么走运
Your body chemistry is slightly less so.
某种名称复杂的酶制造得不够多
Doesn't make enough of a certainabcenzyme that i can't pronounce,
但是很明显对你的肝脏和其他器官很重要
But it's apparently important forabcyour liver and everything else.
用高糖高碳水化合物进行治疗
Treatment is a highabccarb diet rich in sugar.
你原来胖的时候 身体会自行生成这些
When you were a porker,abcyou were self-medicating.
所以 是可以治疗的
So this is treatable.
只需反转胃部旁路abc提高你身体碳水化合物水平
We just have to reverse your gastricabcbypass and get you back on a high carb,
富含葡萄糖的饮食习惯
Glucose-enriched diet.
你最好的状态是很胖的你
The best you you couldabcbe is a lot more you.
张开嘴 飞机来了
Open the hangar. Here comes the plane.
没有别的办法了?
There's nothing else you can try?
有药物可以控制 但是不会痊愈
No. There's a drug that managesabcthe symptoms, but it's not a cure.
试试吧
Let's try that.
你不想做手术?
You don't want to have the surgery?
了解
Understand.
没有多少人肯承认abc和健康比起来更重视美丽
There's not many people who have the guts toabcadmit they'd rather be pretty than healthy.
获得更多收入和性爱
The income's betterabcand you get more action.
我马上进行药物治疗
I'll start you on yourabcdrug treatment right away.
我居然相信了
I bought it.
我竟然相信abc她是为了让人生活得稍微好点
I bought that it was really about tryingabcto make people's lives a little better.
你没想到她这么肤浅么?abc你是整形外科医生 这是人类天性
You're surprised she's superficial? You're aabcplastic surgeon. This is the human condition.
不是 她不正常
No,she's a freak.
每次你为了隆鼻手术给人施麻醉abc是拿他们的生命冒险
Every time you put someone under to bobabctheir nose, you were risking their life.
-什么?abc-不唱歌了 她在好转
- What?abc- No singing. She's better.
不该让我的病人离开病床的
No one was supposed to letabcmy patient leave her bed.
她呼吸困难
She had a respiratory arrest.
我们抢救了20分钟 但是她没挺过来
We coded her nearly 20abcminutes, but she didn't make it.
House是没有感情的小屁孩abc不懂亲密或浪漫
House is an unemotional childabcincapable of intimacy or romance.
相信我吧 结束了 真好
Trust me,it's done. This is perfect.
我喜欢办公桌 很有特点
I like the desk. Lot of character.
不是我订的那个
That's not the one i ordered.
这是我在医学院用的桌子
This is my desk from med school.
放仓库里了?
You have it in storage or something?
我妈妈收起来的
My mom did.
她真好
That was sweet of her to do that.
不是她
She didn't.
她都不知道我在重新装修办公室
My mom has no ideaabci'm redoing my office.
那天晚上我说谎了
I lied to you the other night.
候诊室那个女人abc我并不是因为联想到自己的未来而抓狂
That woman in the waiting room, sheabcdidn't freak me out about my future.
她让我回忆起可怕的过去
She freaked me out about my past.
你的妈妈
Your mother.
看着她死去 一定很痛苦
Must've been horrible watching her die.
我想让她死
I wanted her to die.
她...
She just...
总是凶我
Yelled so much.
毫无理由的 在我朋友面前冲我喊
And for no reason. Just screamedabcat me in front of my friends.
我爸爸向我解释过 她有脑萎缩
My father tried to explain to me thatabcher brain was literally shrinking,
她也不想这样
that she didn't mean it.
是因为疾病 但是我不管
That it was the disease,abcbut i didn't care.
我恨她
I hated her.
我从没跟她道别
I never said good-bye.
她死的时候我还恨着她
And she died with me hating her.
Chase检查过胆囊瘤了么?
Did chase test for the biliary tumor?
据说是阴性
Said it was negative.
离开她的时候还很稳定
Said she was stable when he left her.
该多花点时间 也许能-
Should've found moreabctime.We should've--
House会杀了我们的
house is gonna kill us.
慢慢地
Slowly.
痛苦地
And painfully.
你不仅是白痴 还是骗子
You're not only idiots, you're frauds.
骗人的白痴
Fraudulent idiots.
结果还是个凶手
Fraudulent idioticabckillers, as it turns out.
-House 这都是我的错abc-你的错?当然了
- House,this was reallyabcmy-- - your fault?Yeah!
自以为是 还想当我
For pretending to be me whenabcyou're not even competent.
病人还活着时 你却不揭发他
And your fault for not ratting himabcout while the patient was still alive.
她的病很好治
What she had was easily treatable.
她本该好起来
She could've been fine.
治疗是如此简单
Damn treatment's so simple.
-也许还有救abc-House...
- Might still be possible.abc- House...
House 她已经死了
House,she's clearly dead.
她死了
She was dead.
她没死 她都没病 你个笨蛋
She wasn't dead. Sheabcwasn't even sick, you moron.
说真的 你看她多棒?
Seriously, how good was she?
没接受过演技训练
No formal training.abcAt least not in acting.
你看他们的表情了么?
Did you see their faces?
他们吓坏了吧
I think we may have an analabchygiene violation there.
这个CT怎么回事?
So the ct.
三年前的一个病人的
That was from a patient three years ago.
很难找到的
It was hard to find.
但头发 化妆 串通好Chase和Cameronabc就简单多了
But the hair and make-up, getting chaseabcand cameron to play along, much easier.
我们活该
We deserved it.
我关掉网站
I'll take down the website.
关闭? 别开玩笑了?
Take it down? Are you kidding?
关掉太可惜了
It's way too lucrative to shut it down.
对Chase和我来说abc你用我名字赚来的钱 一半归我
For chase,for me, i earn 50%abcfor letting you use my name.
快点 干活去abc第一笔钱用来付账
Chop chop. Go to work.abcFirst dollars go to expenses.
我雇了这位悲情演员出演两整天
I booked our little thespianabchere for two full days.
我欠她3000块钱
That's three g's i owe her.
你还有三个小时
And you still got 3 hours left.
是么?
Do i?
哥哥买了个椰子abc花了10美分
* brother bought a coconut,abche bought it for a dime *
他妹妹又买了一个abc她换了莱檬
* his sister had another one,abcshe paid it for the lime *
她把莱檬放在椰子里abc她把它们都喝掉
* she put the lime in theabccoconut, she drank 'em both up *
她把莱檬放在椰子里abc她叫了医生 把他唤醒
* put the lime in the coconut, sheabccalled the doctor, woke him up *
我说医生 还有什么我能喝的么
* and said doctor, ain'tabcthere nothin' i can take *
我说医生...
* i said doctor...*